<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Films on anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Films on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 07:17:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>03.25 - Zack Snyder&#39;s Justice League</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/03.25.21_zacksnydersjusticeleague/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 07:17:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/03.25.21_zacksnydersjusticeleague/</guid>
      <description>Well, everyone&amp;rsquo;s talking about it.. Holy crap, I get the hype though. This remux is way more than just an alternate version like you&amp;rsquo;ve seen in the past. This is a whole new retelling of the story. If you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the horrendous version that DC thought would work, then you&amp;rsquo;d probably still have a bad taste in your mouth like I did. Once you get over how upsettingly boring and embarrassing that version was, I emplore you to try this version out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.12 - The Void</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.12.20_thevoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:06:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.12.20_thevoid/</guid>
      <description>The Void (2016) &amp;ldquo;Shortly after delivering a patient to an understaffed hospital, a police officer experiences strange and violent occurences seemingly linked to a group of mysterious hooded figures.&amp;rdquo; - IMDb
Uhuh.
Well shit, buddy, If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a good old raucus time of, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s going on, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really care because look, pretty lights!&amp;rdquo;, then this is the movie for you. It&amp;rsquo;s thematically based off of lovecraftian stuff, and it definitely fits the bill almost perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.11 - Possum</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.11.20_possum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:05:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.11.20_possum/</guid>
      <description>Possum (2018) &amp;ldquo;After returning to his childhood home, a disgraced children&amp;rsquo;s puppeteer is forced to confront his wicked stepfather and the secrets that have tortured his entire life.&amp;rdquo;
Directed by Matthew Holness, starring Sean Harris (Philip), and Alun Armstrong (Maurice &amp;ndash; the stepfather).
HOLY SHIT is this movie heavy or what. This goes through childhood trauma, and how the main character deals with it, and has been dealing with it, and will continue to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.10 - The Wailing</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.10.20_thewailing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:05:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.10.20_thewailing/</guid>
      <description>The Wailing (2016) The recent &amp;ldquo;asian invasion&amp;rdquo; (in reference to the british invasion) of horror films, is probably my most favorite part of these past recent years. The Wailing is no exception to that rule.
Directed by Hong-Jin Na, and starring Do-Won Kwak and Jong-goo.
God this movie does real right. This is a movie that centers around a father and how he copes with a sudden illness entering his town and affecting his daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.08 - Goodnight Mommy</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.08.20_goodnightmommy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.08.20_goodnightmommy/</guid>
      <description>Goodnight Mommy (2014) Damn the Austrians know how to have a good time. &amp;ldquo;Twin boys move to a new home with their mother after she has face changing cosmetic surgery, but under her bandages is someone the children don&amp;rsquo;t recognize.&amp;rdquo;
Starring Lukas and Elias Schwarz as themselves, and Susanne Wuest as Mutter (German for Mother). The movie is in german, and it&amp;rsquo;s based in rural Austria, with some of the most warming visuals of the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.07 - The Hidden</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.07.20_thehidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.07.20_thehidden/</guid>
      <description>The Hidden (1987) I don&amp;rsquo;t mean to freak out and say &amp;ldquo;OMG&amp;rdquo;, but..
OMG I love anything with Kyle MacLachlan in it, everything I watch with him in it, is amazing, and weird, and awkward; just like him. This movie is no different.
Starring that bad boy Kyle (Lloyd Gallagher) alongside Michael Nouri (Tom Beck), as a kind of buddy-cop movie meets the bodysnatchers. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to give this movie away, so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be vague with is as well (Like the other times).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.06 - The Neon Demon</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.06.20_theneondemon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:03:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.06.20_theneondemon/</guid>
      <description>The Neon Demon (2016) Another wonderful film by Nicolas Winding Refn. This guy knows what&amp;rsquo;s up.
Starring the highly esteemed Keanu Reeves, and the young Elle Fanning (almost uncomfortably so), this one is about a lot of things, and I feel it&amp;rsquo;s up to your interpretation where you take it. Elle Fanning plays Jesse, an underage (fittingly so, because she was underage by a year as well while acting this movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.05 - An American Werewolf in London</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.05.20_anamericanwerewolfinlondon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.05.20_anamericanwerewolfinlondon/</guid>
      <description>An American Werewolf in London (1981) Starring Jenny Agutter (Nurse Alex Price), Griffin Dunne (Jack Goodman), and David Naughton (David Kessler), this is the best combination of reality and comedy put into one wholesome package.
It starts off with Jack and David getting into their adventures in rural Britain, happening upon a small town, hoping for a meal to eat. After experiencing some strange interactions with the locals, and a foreshadowing warning (not recieving a meal, upsettingly), they continue onto their journey until misfortune reaches them and Jack is taken from life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.04 - Event Horizon</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.04.20_eventhorizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.04.20_eventhorizon/</guid>
      <description>Event Horizon (1997) Damn does this movie get a lot of slack for it&amp;rsquo;s kind of shitty ending and all, also it kinda goes into the substanceless a bit; but I love it! It&amp;rsquo;s a campy mess! Also the effects are pretty alright considering when it came out.
&amp;ldquo;A rescue crew investigates a spaceship that disappeared into a black hole and has now returned&amp;hellip;with someone or something new on-board.&amp;rdquo;, starring Laurence Fishburne and Sam Neill, this movie, I feel, takes advantage of these two actors beautifully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.03 - The Birds</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.03.20_thebirds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 23:06:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/films/10.03.20_thebirds/</guid>
      <description>The Birds (1963) &amp;ldquo;A wealthy San Francisco socialite pursues a potential boyfriend to a small Northern California town that slowly takes a turn for the bizarre when birds of all kinds suddenly begin to attack people&amp;rdquo;. Directed by Alfred Hitchcock, with a screenplay by Evan Hunter and based off a story by Daphne Du Maurier. Right off the bat, this movie gets an automatic pass from me.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching this film since I was a wee child, and every time I watch it, I still notice something new about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
