<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Films on anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Films on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 07:26:33 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10.02</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.02.20_1408/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 07:26:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.02.20_1408/</guid>
      <description>1408 (2007) 1408 is a much more well known film, about an author who has essentially given up on his life and succumbed to gluttony by only writing books about &amp;lsquo;haunted&amp;rsquo; places and living solo (It&amp;rsquo;s later explained that he left his wife after the death of their daughter). In the shit of his turmoil, he comes across a new lead for a potential &amp;lsquo;scare spot&amp;rsquo; that just so happens to be in New York, where is wife lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.01 - Pee Mak</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.01.20_peemak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 21:29:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.01.20_peemak/</guid>
      <description>Pee Mak (2013) Day 2 of the marathon Pee Mak, Directed by Banjong Pisanthanakun, and Written by Chantavit Dhanasevi, and Nontra Kumwong. This is the first Thai movie I&amp;rsquo;ve seen; and I love it!! This is a Comedy/Horror about a couple of guys coming home from war, only to find out one of their wives is actually a ghost! It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty funny take on usually pretty scary hauntings similar to what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen from Ju-on or The Wailing and so on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>09.30 - November</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/09.30.20_november/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 12:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/09.30.20_november/</guid>
      <description>The Marathon Begins With: November (2017) A quick introduction into what all this is going to be&amp;hellip; Welcome! It is the end of September and the beginning of Fall, and I am here to begin my Spooky Movie Marathon! My current partner is not very accustomed to movies, much less ones that take on a edgier look of the world. I&amp;rsquo;m writing these reviews for my own fun, as all I hope to do really is show my partner the arts and stories that good movies have to tell!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
