<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 07:20:13 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anihilis.ddns.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day_25</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 07:20:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_25/</guid>
      <description>I hate Google and it&amp;rsquo;s not even that personal, like it is; they&amp;rsquo;re a terrible company and need to be split up like five years ago, but that&amp;rsquo;s not what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about today.
Holy shit, I hate android phones. I almost want to go back to a dumb phone, but ironically, somehow those are even less secure now that everyone is tracking everything. Honestly, if Google (and other phone providers) would stop shoving all their own services into their phones I would probably feel a lot better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArchLinux_NewStandard</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/posts/2021/02/archlinux_newstandard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 10:55:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/posts/2021/02/archlinux_newstandard/</guid>
      <description>Arch Linux Setup For My Borg-Collective of Devices My Mission: My ultimate goal every time I do this, is to improve personal performance and security, while also making things as quick and easy to set up as possible. This setup is only temporary (like they all are, really), until I learn to setup NixOS as it provides everything I could ask for within a system.
USB Installation: Just going to plop this in here for a quick reference in case I or you may need it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_24</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 15:12:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_24/</guid>
      <description>It Finished! Thank the lordt! I&amp;rsquo;m grateful that downsizing a video file is a lot easier for my computer, because it only took an hour or so for it to do that after it FINALLY finished color correcting Frozen for me. OMG THO. It came out beautifully! Would I say that it&amp;rsquo;s worth the 2 weeks of processing time? Hell no. I&amp;rsquo;m trying it again on a copy of Maleficent, without the slowest preset turned on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_23</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 08:41:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_23/</guid>
      <description>Fuck you FFmpeg But not really, I love you, please come back.
HOLY SHIT I WISH I HAD A DEDICATED GPU. I am super excited about finally being able to offload all my work from one computer to a more powerful one in the comfort of my own home. The one big downfall however though, is that I get ambitious and decide it&amp;rsquo;s totally fine to just compress a fucking 10bit HDR version of Frozen into an SDR format, without even kind of expecting to have to wait more than two days for the damn thing to finish&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s been almost a whole week now and I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure how far along the process is!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_22</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 13:32:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_22/</guid>
      <description>The Constant Need for Improvement It kills me. I have a dog-damned problem with organization. It&amp;rsquo;s like it&amp;rsquo;s the only thing that will get me off anymore is a well arranged stack of books, or a meticulousely organized filesystem to take it the nerdy way.
I almost find it infuriating at times however, how I am constantly changing what my systems are for and what they need to be able to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_21</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 15:47:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_21/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so I finally install OpenBSD and goddamn, I miss it. Of course I got rid of it after a week and installed Arch Linux with herbstluftwm (my default setup for the past 10 years, despite trying to break it).
I really love OpenBSD, holy shit, it&amp;rsquo;s amazing, well put together, well secured, and has really good hardware support (for Lenovo at least), but has terrible software support. I figure it&amp;rsquo;s because of the security settings, but I can&amp;rsquo;t stand not being able to read out my battery status in live-time, as well as missed the ability to easily handle other filesystems and devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_20 --TW: Death, Cancer</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:18:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_20/</guid>
      <description>I Watched my Grandfather die, and I&amp;rsquo;m starting to think that I still haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten over it. My mom&amp;rsquo;s father, was a shitty human being. He would beat my mom and her sisters, and he was uncomfortably racist, as well as just a terrible influence.
As a kid however, I didn&amp;rsquo;t see all that, I saw a man who was short in attitude, who would stand his ground, and knew what he wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipes</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 19:50:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/recipes/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents:   ⚬ Drinks  Ginger Beer Super Morning Tea Ginger Detox Pumpkin Milk  ⚬ Main Dishes  Mac &amp;lsquo;n Cheese Vegan Chili Roasted Potato Cups w/ Guacamole Cheesy Meatball Bake  ⚬ Sides  Savory Rice  ⚬ Scratch // Basics  Flour Tortillas Easy Pancake Recipe Chia Seed Pudding  ⚬ Desserts  Pumpkin Pie Zucchini Brownies Cookies Peanut Butter Cookies Lefse Vegan Peanut Butter Ice Cream   Drinks Ginger Beer Ingredients  Water Brown Sugar White Sugar Fresh Ginger, Peeled and Minced Kosher Salt Lemon Juice Active Dry Yeast  Directions In a large saucepan combine 1qt water, ½ cup white and brown sugar (each), with a pinch of salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plex Server Update</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/posts/2020/12/plex-server-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 07:04:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/posts/2020/12/plex-server-update/</guid>
      <description>Plex Server Updated [Stable Edition] In my Many Journeys I find myself hopelessly trying to find the cleanest most efficient way to get the things I want done, done. I have hopes to maybe make another one of these soon, instead using FreeBSD as hopefully a final home for all my server needs, but until I become comfortable with that world, I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on using Linux in the most organized way possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_19</title>
      <link>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 15:48:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anihilis.ddns.me/personal_logs/day_19/</guid>
      <description>OpenBSD still eludes me, and i have no idea what to do about it. It&amp;rsquo;s no longer installed on my computer, as I suddenly had things I had to do that work time-sensitive. I want to reinstall it, and I refuse to dual boot anything ever.
The lack of virtualization is also quite odd, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I&amp;rsquo;m going to get past that, cause god-damn is that a sexy OS or what (like, I would love to use it for my server-side work too)?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
