<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 15:48:24 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day_19</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 15:48:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_19/</guid>
      <description>OpenBSD still eludes me, and i have no idea what to do about it. It&amp;rsquo;s no longer installed on my computer, as I suddenly had things I had to do that work time-sensitive. I want to reinstall it, and I refuse to dual boot anything ever.
The lack of virtualization is also quite odd, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I&amp;rsquo;m going to get past that, cause god-damn is that a sexy OS or what (like, I would love to use it for my server-side work too)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_18</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 08:01:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_18/</guid>
      <description>I did it I installed OpenBSD onto my main computer, so far so good! The hardest part for me was setting up my touchpad (I like to turn it off and only use the trackpoint). I&amp;rsquo;ve still got a lot to do before I can call it production ready, but I&amp;rsquo;m really loving it! I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I got cold feet about it, this is the most fun I&amp;rsquo;ve had in a while!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.02</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.02.20_1408/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 07:26:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.02.20_1408/</guid>
      <description>1408 (2007) 1408 is a much more well known film, about an author who has essentially given up on his life and succumbed to gluttony by only writing books about &amp;lsquo;haunted&amp;rsquo; places and living solo (It&amp;rsquo;s later explained that he left his wife after the death of their daughter). In the shit of his turmoil, he comes across a new lead for a potential &amp;lsquo;scare spot&amp;rsquo; that just so happens to be in New York, where is wife lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10.01 - Pee Mak</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.01.20_peemak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 21:29:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/10.01.20_peemak/</guid>
      <description>Pee Mak (2013) Day 2 of the marathon Pee Mak, Directed by Banjong Pisanthanakun, and Written by Chantavit Dhanasevi, and Nontra Kumwong. This is the first Thai movie I&amp;rsquo;ve seen; and I love it!! This is a Comedy/Horror about a couple of guys coming home from war, only to find out one of their wives is actually a ghost! It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty funny take on usually pretty scary hauntings similar to what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen from Ju-on or The Wailing and so on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>09.30 - November</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/09.30.20_november/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 12:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/films/09.30.20_november/</guid>
      <description>The Marathon Begins With: November (2017) A quick introduction into what all this is going to be&amp;hellip; Welcome! It is the end of September and the beginning of Fall, and I am here to begin my Spooky Movie Marathon! My current partner is not very accustomed to movies, much less ones that take on a edgier look of the world. I&amp;rsquo;m writing these reviews for my own fun, as all I hope to do really is show my partner the arts and stories that good movies have to tell!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_17</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 15:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_17/</guid>
      <description>Colour Scheming is a Strange Beast I love pretty colours, but I hate having to set up my system with whole new colour scheming.
I&amp;rsquo;m working on swtiching from the Dracula theme to the Nord theme (I hate saturated work stations&amp;hellip; too busy for long term work). GODDAMN I just wish there was a way to set up all the different config files to respond to the Xresources&amp;hellip;.. hmm&amp;hellip; Maybe I could figure something out&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_16</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 16:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_16/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking, I feel like I should try out OpenBSD. I am finally in a situation where my current setup is fully realized, and fairly stable. Somehow though, all I can think about is how fun it would be to drop this system for something percievably more stable and secure.
The only thing holding me back is the fear of software stability for my photo and video editing, also will switching fuck up my ability to cheat and do some things with DRM?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_15</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 08:51:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_15/</guid>
      <description>Media Sharing So, I have a Plex server, and I use it for myself, and my father, and partner. But they don&amp;rsquo;t ever really use it. My father goes out of his way to use it, and avoids talking about it. What&amp;rsquo;s going on? If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working, they could just let me know what&amp;rsquo;s going on. What&amp;rsquo;s the psychology behind that?? If anyone ever comes across this blog (unlikely) feel free to hit me up and let me know at tasha_saphir@protonmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_14</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:36:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_14/</guid>
      <description>Ugh Shit, yall. I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling pretty crappy the past few days, I even had to skip work!! What am I going to do? The nausea is real. I&amp;rsquo;m fairly certain it isn&amp;rsquo;t COVID. I have my suspicions that it&amp;rsquo;s maybe all the tear gas and such in the air right now, along with all the forest fires right now. I&amp;rsquo;m in Portland, for reference.
 In other news, I&amp;rsquo;ve never been more nervous about sirens than I am during these times&amp;hellip; I wonder why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plex Server Setup-notes</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/09/plex-server-setup-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 12:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/09/plex-server-setup-notes/</guid>
      <description>Plex Server Setup A Walkthrough I have finally found my perfect Plex setup, as shown in my post about setting up Artix (the subcategory about Servers is the example). My preferred setup is a boxed in Plex setup, to prevent access unwanted access from the UPnP ports.
Beginning Notes I believe we can collect installation notes from the https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artixandrunit-install/. I prefer to avoid encryption so I can restart the computer remotely.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
