<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 08:51:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_15</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 08:51:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_15/</guid>
      <description>Media Sharing So, I have a Plex server, and I use it for myself, and my father, and partner. But they don&amp;rsquo;t ever really use it. My father goes out of his way to use it, and avoids talking about it. What&amp;rsquo;s going on? If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working, they could just let me know what&amp;rsquo;s going on. What&amp;rsquo;s the psychology behind that?? If anyone ever comes across this blog (unlikely) feel free to hit me up and let me know at tasha_saphir@protonmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_14</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:36:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_14/</guid>
      <description>Ugh Shit, yall. I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling pretty crappy the past few days, I even had to skip work!! What am I going to do? The nausea is real. I&amp;rsquo;m fairly certain it isn&amp;rsquo;t COVID. I have my suspicions that it&amp;rsquo;s maybe all the tear gas and such in the air right now, along with all the forest fires right now. I&amp;rsquo;m in Portland, for reference.
 In other news, I&amp;rsquo;ve never been more nervous about sirens than I am during these times&amp;hellip; I wonder why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plex Server Setup-notes</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/09/plex-server-setup-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 12:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/09/plex-server-setup-notes/</guid>
      <description>Plex Server Setup A Walkthrough I have finally found my perfect Plex setup, as shown in my post about setting up Artix (the subcategory about Servers is the example). My preferred setup is a boxed in Plex setup, to prevent access unwanted access from the UPnP ports.
Beginning Notes I believe we can collect installation notes from the https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artixandrunit-install/. I prefer to avoid encryption so I can restart the computer remotely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_13</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 07:07:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_13/</guid>
      <description>Getting Away Sitting here on day 1 Million or so of our COVID trials, I watch Calvary, a film from 2014 with an all star cast of european actors (I don&amp;rsquo;t dare assume where they&amp;rsquo;re all from, I&amp;rsquo;m American and stupid). The film is about a Priest who is forced into a situation where a man angry at the Catholic church decides to kill a good priest for attention because of all the evils the bad priests have done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_12</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 11:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_12/</guid>
      <description>P.O.S. Point of Sale System I am working on a Proof of Concept POS System for my work, because I am tired of the constant problems presenting themselves when I least want them to. I am looking to switch to a completely disconnected, open source solution for work with multiple systems across two states and 5 stores. They are currently using very outdated (almost XP era) PCs with windows 10 locked down, with a shit POS system, and a terrible set up of permissions for apps and users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_11</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 09:28:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_11/</guid>
      <description>Is There a Better One? Is there a better version? Is there Another Version? Are there really infinite realities? Is my old boss really Batman?
Just a couple of questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artix and Runit Install</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artix-and-runit-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 01:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artix-and-runit-install/</guid>
      <description>Switching to Artix Personal Walkthrough What&amp;rsquo;s my Mission? I want to improve performance, security, and declutter my system by subverting Systemd. I also intend to encrypt my hard drive, as well as partial encryption of my internet traffic, whilst also using flatpak on large-library projects to avoid any system breakages.
USB Installation Grab the ISO from ArtixLinux.org, install with:
 sudo dd bs=4M if=path/to/image-runit.iso of=/dev/sdx status=progress oflag=sync
 Installation &amp;ndash; Prepare When booting into a UEFI Laptop (any laptop made in the past 8 years just about), make sure it is in UEFI mode, despite how you might feel, it is a form of check, and good for software security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_10</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 16:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_10/</guid>
      <description>Artix Linux Security (Should This be put in Posts? Y.O.L.O. why not Both?) I&amp;rsquo;m on tiling! No buttons for me!! So yeah, I basically completely switched to using cli everything, and so for networking I am using NetworkManager, it&amp;rsquo;s been weird having to get used to it&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s like it&amp;rsquo;s too easy for me&amp;hellip; that I can&amp;rsquo;t figure it out? Like it makes sense, but&amp;hellip; I can&amp;rsquo;t use my intuiting? Anyways, I still can&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to use it with openvpn, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to use wireguard without a file&amp;hellip; and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to figure out if I have to make the file or what&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_09</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 13:24:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_09/</guid>
      <description>Switched My OS!! Huzzah! I have done it! I am free from Solus Linux!
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I love the damned Operating System, I just started feeling claustrophobic with the systemd and the perfect UX and clean UI&amp;hellip; it was just&amp;hellip;. too perfect&amp;hellip;
So what did I switch to? I did a base install of Artix Linux! I love it so far! I went with the runit instance, because it seemed to have the best server/desktop useability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_07</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 08:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_07/</guid>
      <description>Am I Fat? I hate being told what to do with my health, I&amp;rsquo;ve been living with eating disorder all my life, and I like to think that I have gotten a grasp of things, have a logic, and a method. Which makes it all the more upsetting with someone comes around and decides they have to authority to tell me what to do with my body.
I don&amp;rsquo;t care what you think!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>