<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal_logs on anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal_logs on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 11:51:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_12</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 11:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_12/</guid>
      <description>P.O.S. Point of Sale System I am working on a Proof of Concept POS System for my work, because I am tired of the constant problems presenting themselves when I least want them to. I am looking to switch to a completely disconnected, open source solution for work with multiple systems across two states and 5 stores. They are currently using very outdated (almost XP era) PCs with windows 10 locked down, with a shit POS system, and a terrible set up of permissions for apps and users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_11</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 09:28:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_11/</guid>
      <description>Is There a Better One? Is there a better version? Is there Another Version? Are there really infinite realities? Is my old boss really Batman?
Just a couple of questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_10</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 16:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_10/</guid>
      <description>Artix Linux Security (Should This be put in Posts? Y.O.L.O. why not Both?) I&amp;rsquo;m on tiling! No buttons for me!! So yeah, I basically completely switched to using cli everything, and so for networking I am using NetworkManager, it&amp;rsquo;s been weird having to get used to it&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s like it&amp;rsquo;s too easy for me&amp;hellip; that I can&amp;rsquo;t figure it out? Like it makes sense, but&amp;hellip; I can&amp;rsquo;t use my intuiting? Anyways, I still can&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to use it with openvpn, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to use wireguard without a file&amp;hellip; and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to figure out if I have to make the file or what&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_09</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 13:24:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_09/</guid>
      <description>Switched My OS!! Huzzah! I have done it! I am free from Solus Linux!
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I love the damned Operating System, I just started feeling claustrophobic with the systemd and the perfect UX and clean UI&amp;hellip; it was just&amp;hellip;. too perfect&amp;hellip;
So what did I switch to? I did a base install of Artix Linux! I love it so far! I went with the runit instance, because it seemed to have the best server/desktop useability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_07</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 08:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_07/</guid>
      <description>Am I Fat? I hate being told what to do with my health, I&amp;rsquo;ve been living with eating disorder all my life, and I like to think that I have gotten a grasp of things, have a logic, and a method. Which makes it all the more upsetting with someone comes around and decides they have to authority to tell me what to do with my body.
I don&amp;rsquo;t care what you think!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_06</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:04:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_06/</guid>
      <description>Embarrassment How often do you embarrass yourself? I do almost hourly, often I&amp;rsquo;m embarrassed way before I even begin doing the thing that caused such hard to spell feelings. For me, however, this feeling is often a side-effect of my anxiety. For instance, right now; I&amp;rsquo;m just sitting here, eating taquitos, writing this post. All I&amp;rsquo;m think about though, is my partner coming home, and seeing the empty box&amp;hellip;. Also it&amp;rsquo;s the only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve eaten today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_05</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 04:17:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_05/</guid>
      <description>Using Solus I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on the Solus operating system (base kernel of Linux) for several months now (recently returned to Linux and all relevant things along from using a Macbook for a minute), as a laptop system, as well as for my server (boy was that a mistake).
I&amp;rsquo;ve reached that point however, where everything is superbly streamlined, and everything works without error, ever. AND IT&amp;rsquo;S SO BORING. I&amp;rsquo;ve always had the issue of being bored of my tech when I&amp;rsquo;m not messing with it from the most basic levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_04</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 08:03:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_04/</guid>
      <description>Work can be a Bitch Goddamn, work is a bitch. During all this COVID bullshit, I have to sell people sex toys like nothing is going on. Everyone wants to feel up the toys, they wanna come in a use our arcades, they wanna come in WITH NO MASK.
I don&amp;rsquo;t care what you think about masks or social distancing, it&amp;rsquo;s important to respect other&amp;rsquo;s wishes and personal space. Fuck you if you refuse to wear a mask to prove some bullshit point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_03</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 07:40:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_03/</guid>
      <description>My Dream for Dystopia I long that one day, we will be free from the confines of a rigged Republic and a suffocating Capitalist regime. No, but like, seriously. I really want all out anarchy. Not Mad Max folley, but like&amp;hellip;. Waterworld&amp;hellip;. or Willow. Fuck Star Wars though. I would rather suffer in the Sarlack pit than have to deal with that confusing mess. You&amp;rsquo;re either living in a Dictatorship, or in a society of people with stick-up-your-butt-itis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_02</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 10:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_02/</guid>
      <description>Day two on this blog&amp;hellip; My partner is signing up for Medicare right now, and I&amp;rsquo;m working on my internet security sheet. Her father is in town to help her out, I enjoy the company. With FISA being put to good use in Portland right now, I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel comfortable going outside right now. I don&amp;rsquo;t care if I&amp;rsquo;m a goody two-shoes that doesn&amp;rsquo;t do anything, I have friends, and there are others out there who are doing very dangerous things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>