<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal_logs on anihilis ddns</title>
    <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal_logs on anihilis ddns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:04:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_06</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 10:04:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_06/</guid>
      <description>Embarrassment How often do you embarrass yourself? I do almost hourly, often I&amp;rsquo;m embarrassed way before I even begin doing the thing that caused such hard to spell feelings. For me, however, this feeling is often a side-effect of my anxiety. For instance, right now; I&amp;rsquo;m just sitting here, eating taquitos, writing this post. All I&amp;rsquo;m think about though, is my partner coming home, and seeing the empty box&amp;hellip;. Also it&amp;rsquo;s the only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve eaten today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_05</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 04:17:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_05/</guid>
      <description>Using Solus I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on the Solus operating system (base kernel of Linux) for several months now (recently returned to Linux and all relevant things along from using a Macbook for a minute), as a laptop system, as well as for my server (boy was that a mistake).
I&amp;rsquo;ve reached that point however, where everything is superbly streamlined, and everything works without error, ever. AND IT&amp;rsquo;S SO BORING. I&amp;rsquo;ve always had the issue of being bored of my tech when I&amp;rsquo;m not messing with it from the most basic levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_04</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 08:03:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_04/</guid>
      <description>Work can be a Bitch Goddamn, work is a bitch. During all this COVID bullshit, I have to sell people sex toys like nothing is going on. Everyone wants to feel up the toys, they wanna come in a use our arcades, they wanna come in WITH NO MASK.
I don&amp;rsquo;t care what you think about masks or social distancing, it&amp;rsquo;s important to respect other&amp;rsquo;s wishes and personal space. Fuck you if you refuse to wear a mask to prove some bullshit point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_03</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 07:40:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_03/</guid>
      <description>My Dream for Dystopia I long that one day, we will be free from the confines of a rigged Republic and a suffocating Capitalist regime. No, but like, seriously. I really want all out anarchy. Not Mad Max folley, but like&amp;hellip;. Waterworld&amp;hellip;. or Willow. Fuck Star Wars though. I would rather suffer in the Sarlack pit than have to deal with that confusing mess. You&amp;rsquo;re either living in a Dictatorship, or in a society of people with stick-up-your-butt-itis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_02</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 10:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_02/</guid>
      <description>Day two on this blog&amp;hellip; My partner is signing up for Medicare right now, and I&amp;rsquo;m working on my internet security sheet. Her father is in town to help her out, I enjoy the company. With FISA being put to good use in Portland right now, I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel comfortable going outside right now. I don&amp;rsquo;t care if I&amp;rsquo;m a goody two-shoes that doesn&amp;rsquo;t do anything, I have friends, and there are others out there who are doing very dangerous things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day_01</title>
      <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 06:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/personal_logs/day_01/</guid>
      <description>AHHHH COVID Holy shit.
So now what? It&amp;rsquo;s almost the end of July, I have friends and family messaging me checking in, as if all of Portland were under complete turmoil. What?? I mean, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of protests going on. There&amp;rsquo;s also a lot of people getting infected, and lots of people dying from both problems. HOWEVER. I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending all my time inside, due to my partner, needing an intel facility to live in, essentially.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>