<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on anihilis ddns</title>
        <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on anihilis ddns</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 07:04:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Plex Server Update</title>
            <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/12/plex-server-update/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 07:04:45 -0800</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/12/plex-server-update/</guid>
            <description>Plex Server Updated [Stable Edition] In my Many Journeys I find myself hopelessly trying to find the cleanest most efficient way to get the things I want done, done. I have hopes to maybe make another one of these soon, instead using FreeBSD as hopefully a final home for all my server needs, but until I become comfortable with that world, I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on using Linux in the most organized way possible.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="plex-server-updated-stable-edition">Plex Server Updated [Stable Edition]</h1>
<h2 id="in-my-many-journeys">In my Many Journeys</h2>
<p>I find myself hopelessly trying to find the cleanest most efficient way to get the things I want done, done. I have hopes to maybe make another one of these soon, instead using FreeBSD as hopefully a final home for all my server needs, but until I become comfortable with that world, I&rsquo;m going to focus on using Linux in the most organized way possible.</p>
<h2 id="a-quick-explanation">A quick explanation:</h2>
<p>If you&rsquo;re a regular user of linux and partake in the social media and the peoples involved with the Linux community, you probably have heard about people wanted the smallest installs with the least amount of packages and so forth and so forth. I have a similar neuroticism, but mine is simply that of organization.<br>
I feel that linux has a habit of cluttering itself over time. I prefer to know what is on my system, and I don&rsquo;t want random cruft building up over time, be it old packages (like in Arch how it holds onto previous versions of packages), or a loss of understanding the resources set up (human knowledge error). Linux honestly has too many options, not like GNU options (one package/piece of code for action), but just on the system already. I want a system where I can do everything with single commands. In Linux these days, there&rsquo;s kernel supported legacy items, as well as the all encompassing, always install SystemD. For instance, cron jobs were a thing that people used to do (and a lot still do), but SystemD, which is installed on all major distributions, also have a timer system.<br>
I have remedied this mostly with my current laptop setup (because I would murder someone if I had to live knowing all that extra garbage was on my system) by simply using only SystemD for all my needs, from mounting, to timers, to user management. I hate it, but it&rsquo;s better that just using it to boot and other stuff for other things, while I have all this unused code on my kernel and in my system.<br>
With the BSDs of the world, they are very small, the kernel only including things you absolutely need, and the software count is limited to ports from linux and anything the devs feel is absolutely important. It&rsquo;s also nice how everything is cohesive and in order, from the locations of the binaries to the settings, and GODDAMN do I love how there&rsquo;s never more than two solutions to one problem. I STG I&rsquo;m tired of having so many ways to fix one problem on my system, and knowing that I can go around and accidently do one of those other things not knowing I&rsquo;m screwing with another part of my system!<br>
Anyways, I&rsquo;m done ranting now, I got a little keyboard rage there&hellip;.</p>
<h2 id="beginning-notes">Beginning Notes</h2>
<p>I now have the world&rsquo;s greatest dotfiles repo, and I will never share it because it has so much personal info as well as application files that I&rsquo;m not sure of the shareability of, that I&rsquo;m not willing to vet to share. However, I&rsquo;m going to link it <a href="https://github.com/natty-warhol/dotfiles-Github">here</a>, for my own convenience. Maybe I&rsquo;ll make a second public neutered git or something later, but this is where we&rsquo;re at.</p>
<p>I currently have quite the set up of hard-drives. I currently do not have a RAID or any other kind of redundancy. I only carry media and personal files on them, nothing super mission critical (y&rsquo;know, besides to my boredom levels). Currently, this is what it looks like, no judgements:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>/dev/sda -&gt; /home/USER/Pictures (1Tb)<br>
/dev/sdb -&gt; System</p>
<blockquote>
<p>/dev/sdb1 -&gt; /boot/efi (300M)<br>
/dev/sdb2 -&gt; / (???)<br>
/dev/sdb3 -&gt; SWAP (double RAM)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>/dev/sdc -&gt; /home/USER/Videos/Movies (5Tb)<br>
/dev/sdd -&gt; /home/USER/Music (2Tb)<br>
/dev/sde -&gt; /home/USER/Videos/TV (5Tb)<br>
/dev/sdh -&gt; /home/USER/Videos/;) (150Gb)</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="user-accounts">User Accounts</h2>
<p>This time around I was lacking in inspiration and took to the internet. Decided to name things after Lovecraftian places and creatures.. Which kinda fits my solar theme with my mobile devices.<br>
Also this time around, I decided to scrap the multiple users with the Docker BS (I grew tired of Docker, with Plex, you give up a lot of accessibility features). Instead I went ahead with creating one user with root priv. and another user without. I&rsquo;m SSHing into the non-rootable user, and then using the <code>su</code> command.<br>
I&rsquo;m doing this to deal with the confusion, I also ended up having trials and errors with ownership privileges, and transferring files between accounts was a nightmare.<br>
The rootable account has all the services in it&rsquo;s name, and I can only perform maintenance remotely (unless remoting in with teamviewer).</p>
<h2 id="internet-access-and-security">Internet Access and Security</h2>
<p>This time around, I went the easy way with Debian and XFCE as a desktop right out the box. I&rsquo;m using the standard gui NetworkManager connected to Ethernet (with a simultaneous WiFi for the VM we&rsquo;ll talk about later). I have it set up to access the Quad9 DNS only (no more 1.1.1.1).<br>
For the firewall I&rsquo;m still using the trusty UFW (fuck iptables, and thank god for simplicity of use). I stick with the default of deny, and a limit on 64 (my SSH port of choice).</p>
<pre><code>To                         Action      From  
---  
syncthing                  ALLOW       Anywhere                  
64/tcp                     LIMIT       Anywhere                  
6985/tcp                   ALLOW       Anywhere                  
6985/udp                   ALLOW       Anywhere                  
plexmediaserver            ALLOW       Anywhere                  
6890:6999/tcp              ALLOW       Anywhere                  
6890:6999/udp              ALLOW       Anywhere                  
Samba                      ALLOW       Anywhere                  
syncthing (v6)             ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)             
64/tcp (v6)                LIMIT       Anywhere (v6)             
6985/tcp (v6)              ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)             
6985/udp (v6)              ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)             
plexmediaserver (v6)       ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)             
6890:6999/tcp (v6)         ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)             
6890:6999/udp (v6)         ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)             
Samba (v6)                 ALLOW       Anywhere (v6)  
</code></pre><h2 id="plex-installation">Plex Installation</h2>
<p>Luckily, Debian has a PPA for direct Plex updates! just go to the <a href="https://knapsu.eu/plex/">website</a>, install the deb file they provide, and then the mirror comes with it. Wamo-bamo.</p>
<h2 id="virtual-machine-for-media-collection">Virtual Machine for Media Collection</h2>
<p>In order to offload all the work I do for the server on my laptop I decided to turn my server into two computers instead of just getting a cheap other one. I&rsquo;m using Virtualbox (My server is a Galago Pro, it can&rsquo;t even VM right, I&rsquo;m not gonna waste my time with QEMU for that. I&rsquo;ve set the network up to bridged, and have my private VPN service that I connect to from the VM, and then can SSH into it from my laptop or the other server to use any of the services I choose to for collection.<br>
Generally speaking, I will prefer to use Arch or something derivative for this, just because updates are good for security, especially if you&rsquo;re gonna be doing a lot of downloading other&rsquo;s materials.</p>
<h2 id="le-fin-for-now">Le Fin&hellip; For Now&hellip;.</h2>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Plex Server Setup //Redacted//</title>
            <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/09/plex-server-setup-/redacted/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 12:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/09/plex-server-setup-/redacted/</guid>
            <description>A Walkthrough I have finally found my perfect Plex setup, as shown in my post about setting up Artix (the subcategory about Servers is the example). My preferred setup is a boxed in Plex setup, to prevent access unwanted access from the UPnP ports.
Beginning Notes I believe we can collect installation notes from the https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artixandrunit-install/. I prefer to avoid encryption so I can restart the computer remotely.
Mapping looks something like this:</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="a-walkthrough">A Walkthrough</h2>
<p>I have finally found my perfect Plex setup, as shown in my post about setting up Artix (the subcategory about Servers is the example). My preferred setup is a boxed in Plex setup, to prevent access unwanted access from the UPnP ports.</p>
<h3 id="beginning-notes">Beginning Notes</h3>
<p>I believe we can collect installation notes from the <!-- raw HTML omitted --><a href="https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artixandrunit-install/">https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artixandrunit-install/</a><!-- raw HTML omitted -->. I prefer to avoid encryption so I can restart the computer remotely.</p>
<p>Mapping looks something like this:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>/dev/sda</p>
<blockquote>
<p>/dev/sda1 -&gt; /boot<br>
/dev/sda2 -&gt; /boot/efi<br>
/dev/sda3 -&gt; /<br>
/dev/sda4 -&gt; SWAP<br>
/dev/sdb1 -&gt; /home/plex/media/Movies<br>
/dev/sdc1 -&gt; /home/plex/media/TV<br>
/dev/sdd1 -&gt; /home/plex/meida/Music</p>
</blockquote>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="user-accounts-set-up">User Accounts Set Up:</h3>
<p>You should only ever use <code>root</code> for administration and installation purposes. So in this case, we are setting up a very hard password for it, and writing it down somewhere to never be used again.</p>
<p>I like to give myself a sudo-able user for SSHing into with, when setting up accounts, this is the only one that should have sudo permissions. Following the creation of the <em>administrative</em> account, we can go on to the Plex account.</p>
<p>With the media/Plex account, I like to give it almost no permissions, I give it access to read the media hard drives (which should be mounted to this account anyways), and this is where the docker server will be planted.</p>
<h3 id="good-measures">Good Measures</h3>
<p>Before setting up any port forwarding or any internet access, I like to set up security measures. There will be no VPN as this will cause my ports to be blocked from plex. Instead, I change the DNS either to 1.1.1.1 or Quad9, as well as set up UFW.</p>
<p>With UFW I set the defaults to deny all incoming except for a designated plex and SSH port (which should be changed from the default ports to at least 4 digit ports (5 in Plex&rsquo;s case)</p>
<p>After this, Things should be fine, all the internet access that will be allowd to this device anyway will be limited.</p>
<h3 id="plex-installation">Plex Installation</h3>
<p>As the administrative user, go ahead an install docker as well as the docker init script (runit for me).</p>
<pre><code>pacman -S docker docker-runit  
ln -s /etc/runit/sv/docker /run/runit/service  
</code></pre><p>Docker install and set-up instruction can be found <!-- raw HTML omitted -->here<!-- raw HTML omitted -->.</p>
<p>Required commands to remember after setup are:</p>
<pre><code>docker start plex  
docker stop plex  
</code></pre><p>Simply for restarting and updating.</p>
<p>With the commands run from that website, the VM will only be able to read the files on the media drives, and no other drives on the system.</p>
<p>Voila!</p>
<h3 id="ps">P.S.</h3>
<p>After you&rsquo;re all done, there are some tools I can recommend for you!<br>
Since the server will basically only be able to read the media files, I have ffmpeg set up with H.265 for compression when needed through the administrative account.</p>
<p>And for health checking I use glances mostly (it shows the temps).</p>
<p>For media transfers, I recommend Syncthing, as it will allow you to use local internet. Just remember to check your sync options, I always feel more comfortable when my sync folders are one way read/sync.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Artix and Runit Install</title>
            <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artix-and-runit-install/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 01:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/08/artix-and-runit-install/</guid>
            <description>Switching to Artix Personal Walkthrough What&amp;rsquo;s my Mission? I want to improve performance, security, and declutter my system by subverting Systemd. I also intend to encrypt my hard drive, as well as partial encryption of my internet traffic, whilst also using flatpak on large-library projects to avoid any system breakages.
USB Installation Grab the ISO from ArtixLinux.org, install with:
 sudo dd bs=4M if=path/to/image-runit.iso of=/dev/sdx status=progress oflag=sync
 Installation &amp;ndash; Prepare When booting into a UEFI Laptop (any laptop made in the past 8 years just about), make sure it is in UEFI mode, despite how you might feel, it is a form of check, and good for software security.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="switching-to-artix">Switching to Artix</h1>
<h2 id="personal-walkthrough">Personal Walkthrough</h2>
<h2 id="whats-my-mission">What&rsquo;s my Mission?</h2>
<p>I want to improve performance, security, and declutter my system by subverting Systemd. I also intend to encrypt my hard drive, as well as partial encryption of my internet traffic, whilst also using flatpak on large-library projects to avoid any system breakages.</p>
<h2 id="usb-installation">USB Installation</h2>
<p>Grab the ISO from ArtixLinux.org, install with:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>sudo dd bs=4M if=path/to/image-runit.iso of=/dev/sdx status=progress oflag=sync</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="installation----prepare">Installation &ndash; Prepare</h2>
<p>When booting into a UEFI Laptop (any laptop made in the past 8 years just about), make sure it is in UEFI mode, despite how you might feel, it is a form of check, and good for software security. Without booting into the USB without UEFI mode, installation may not work.</p>
<p>Ensure that there is an internet connection. The easiest way to do so, is to use an ethernet cable. Otherwise&hellip;. <em>shrugs</em> I&rsquo;m not sure what to do with this one, I didn&rsquo;t really look into it because I&rsquo;m lazy and they didn&rsquo;t use netctl like Mainline Arch does.</p>
<h2 id="installation">Installation</h2>
<h3 id="formatting">Formatting</h3>
<p>Got to use Luks Encryption!</p>
<pre><code>parted /dev/sdx  
mklabel gpt  
mkpart ESP fat32 1Mib 512Mib  
set 1 boot on  
name 1 efi  
</code></pre><pre><code>mkpart primary linux-swap 512Mib 8Gb  
name 2 swap  
</code></pre><pre><code>mkpart primary 8Gb 100%  
set 3 lvm on  
name 3 lvm  
print  
</code></pre><pre><code>modprobe dm-crypt
modprobe dm-mod
</code></pre><pre><code>cryptsetup luksFormat -v -s 512 -h sha512 /dev/sdx3  
</code></pre><pre><code>cryptsetup open &lt;device&gt; &lt;name&gt;
</code></pre><p><em><!-- raw HTML omitted --></em> is the device to create under /dev/mapper<br>
<em><!-- raw HTML omitted --></em> is the encrypted device</p>
<p><strong>Example: cryptsetup open /dev/sdx3 luks_lvm</strong></p>
<h3 id="partition-configuration">Partition Configuration</h3>
<p>Create physical volume</p>
<pre><code>pvcreate /dev/mapper/luks_lvm  
</code></pre><pre><code>vgcreate artix /dev/mapper/luks_lvm  
</code></pre><pre><code>lvcreate -n root -L XXG arch  
lvcreate -n home -L XXG arch  
</code></pre><pre><code>Format partitions  
mkfs.fat -F32 /dev/sdx1
mkfs.ext4 -L root /dev/mapper/arch-root
mkfs.ext4 -L home /dev/mapper/arch-home
mkswap /dev/sdx2
</code></pre><h3 id="mount-partitions">Mount Partitions</h3>
<pre><code>swapon /dev/sdx2  
mount /dev/mapper/arch-root /mnt  
mkdir -p /mnt/{home,boot}  
mount /dev/sdx1 /mnt/boot  
mount /dev/mapper/arch-home /mnt/home  
mkdir /mnt/boot/efi  
</code></pre><pre><code>lsblk -f  
</code></pre><h3 id="install-linux">Install Linux</h3>
<pre><code>basestrap /mnt base base-devel runit elogind-runit vim htop openssh linux-zen linux-firmware  
fstabgen -U /mnt &gt;&gt; /mnt/etc/fstab  
</code></pre><pre><code>artools-chroot /mnt  
</code></pre><h3 id="base-configuration">Base Configuration</h3>
<pre><code>ln -sf /usr/share/zoneinfo/America/Los_Angeles  
hwclock --systohc  
</code></pre><pre><code>vim /etc/locale.gen  
locale-gen  
</code></pre><pre><code>vim /etc/locale.conf  
export LANG=&quot;en_US.UTF-8&quot;  
export LC_COLLATE=&quot;C&quot;  
</code></pre><h4 id="boot-loader">Boot Loader</h4>
<pre><code>pacman -S grub os-prober efibootmgr  
grub-install --target=x86_64-efi --efi-directory=/boot --bootloader-id=grub  
grub-mkconfig -o /boot/grub/grub.cfg  
</code></pre><h4 id="users">Users</h4>
<pre><code>passwd  
</code></pre><pre><code>useradd -m user  
passwd user  
</code></pre><h4 id="network-configuration">Network Configuration</h4>
<pre><code>vim /etc/hostname  
*insert hostname here*  
pacman -S dhcpcd networkmanager networkmanager-openvpn 
</code></pre><h3 id="all-done">All Done!</h3>
<pre><code>exit  
umount -R /mnt  
reboot  
</code></pre><h2 id="post-installation-with-xorg">Post Installation with Xorg</h2>
<pre><code>pacman -S xorg libva-utils libmfx intel-media-driver intel-gmmlib xf86-video-intel vulkan-intel intel-ucode herbstluftwm git trizen dzen2 dmenu polybar pass gpgme gnupg flatpak firefox htop libdvdcss libbluray rtorrent pulseaudio pavucontrol pamixer pulseaudio-bluetooth bluez-tools bluez-utils xdotool
  
trizen -S rxvt-unicode-pixbuf-patched urxvt-tabbedex hosts-update plex-media-player 
  
git clone https://github.com/natty-warhol/dotfiles-Github.git  
</code></pre><h3 id="firefox-setup">Firefox Setup</h3>
<pre><code>git clone https://github.com/Perflyst/firefox-privacy-profile.git  
</code></pre><p>Create new Firefox Profile, ensure you can remember the profile association. Then copy the files in the folder into the profile folder in your /home directory.</p>
<p>go to <!-- raw HTML omitted -->HexDSL&rsquo;s Gitlab<!-- raw HTML omitted --> for extension options and so on.</p>
<h3 id="firefox-alternative">Firefox Alternative</h3>
<p>An alternative to firefox (for lighter weight needs) you can use tabbed with vimb</p>
<pre><code>pacman -S vimb  
trizen -S tabbed  
</code></pre><p>then execute with</p>
<pre><code>tabbed vimb -e  
</code></pre><h3 id="flatpak----thinkpad">Flatpak &ndash; Thinkpad</h3>
<pre><code>flatpak install com.makemkv.MakeMKV com.rawtherapee.RawTherapee org.gimp.GIMP org.inkscape.Inkscape net.jami.Jami org.audacityteam.Audacity org.signal.Signal org.telegram.desktop org.kde.Kdenlive 
</code></pre><h3 id="fingerprint-reader----thinkpad">Fingerprint Reader &ndash; Thinkpad</h3>
<pre><code>trizen -S fwupd usbutils fprintd imagemagick  
</code></pre><p>Edit the config files inside of /etc/pam.d/</p>
<p>system-local-login</p>
<pre><code>auth	sufficient	pam_fprintd.so
auth	sufficient	pam_thinkfinger.so
</code></pre><p>su</p>
<pre><code>auth	sufficient	pam_fprintd.so
</code></pre><p>sudo</p>
<pre><code>auth	sufficient	pam_fprintd.so  
</code></pre><p>physlock</p>
<pre><code>auth	sufficient	pam_fprintd.so
</code></pre><h2 id="server-extrasedits">Server Extras/Edits</h2>
<p>**Basic Hard Drive Configuration: **
SDA1 /
SDA2 /home
SDA3 SWAP
SDB1 /home/plex/media/Music
SDC1 /home/plex/media/Movies
SDD1 /hom/plex/media/TV\ Shows</p>
<p>**User Accounts Set Up: **
Root &ndash;never touch after setup<br>
Media_XYZ &ndash;lightly uplifted account for SSH access as well as X server.
Plex &ndash;minimal root priviliges, don&rsquo;t forget to chown plex:plex mounted media drives.</p>
<p><strong>NZBGet</strong></p>
<pre><code>sudo pacman -S nzbget  
sudo useradd -m -G nzbget
</code></pre><pre><code>sudo vim /var/lib/nzbget/.nzbget  
</code></pre><blockquote>
<p>MainDir=/var/lib/nzbget
DestDir=/var/lib/nzbget/Downloads</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So on, So on, until all the addresses are set to /var/lib/nzbget&hellip;<br>
Account and server setup is backed up
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->Personal note:
- Try to add the user with &ldquo;-d /home/$USER/Downloads/NZBGet&rdquo;
- Move the directories in /var/lib to the home directory for nzbget
- Move the username and password to a text file, and link from the main config
<!-- raw HTML omitted --></p>
<p><strong>Don&rsquo;t Forget!1</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>noip ping script for DNS UPnP</li>
<li>Setup Syncthing with runit daemon</li>
<li>Set SSHD to port 64</li>
<li>Setup UFW with runit</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="plex-docker-setup">Plex Docker Setup</h3>
<pre><code>pacman -S docker docker-runit  
ln -s /etc/runit/sv/docker /run/runit/service  
</code></pre><p>Docker install and set-up instruction can be found <!-- raw HTML omitted -->here<!-- raw HTML omitted -->.</p>
<p>Required commands to remember after setup are:</p>
<pre><code>docker start plex  
docker stop plex  
</code></pre><p>Simply for restarting and updating.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Internet Security (Active Article)</title>
            <link>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/07/internet-security-active-article/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 05:07:07 -0700</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://natty-warhol.github.io/posts/2020/07/internet-security-active-article/</guid>
            <description>Hiding From the Internet &amp;ndash; Making a Plan * Information largely *taken* from the EFF1
 What do you want to hide? How bad are the consequences if I fail? How Likely is it That I will Need to Protect it? How Much Trouble am I Willing to go Through to try to Prevent Potential Consequences? Security Planning as a Regular Practice How far are you Willing to go? Simple Security Measures  Browser Add-ons Firewalls Encryption in Communication   Moderate Difficulty Actions  GPG - Encrypt on your own!</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="hiding-from-the-internet----making-a-plan">Hiding From the Internet &ndash; Making a Plan</h2>
<p><!-- raw HTML omitted -->* Information largely *taken* from the EFF<!-- raw HTML omitted --> <sup id="fnref:1"><a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1</a></sup></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="#what-do-you-want-to-hide">What do you want to hide?</a></li>
<li><a href="#how-bad-are-the-consequences-if-i-fail">How bad are the consequences if I fail?</a></li>
<li><a href="#how-likely-is-it-that-i-will-need-to-protect-it">How Likely is it That I will Need to Protect it?</a></li>
<li><a href="#how-much-am-i-willing-to-go-through-to-try-to-prevent-potential-consequences">How Much Trouble am I Willing to go Through to try to Prevent Potential Consequences?</a></li>
<li><a href="#security-planning-as-a-regular-practice">Security Planning as a Regular Practice</a></li>
<li><a href="#how-far-are-you-willing-to-go">How far are you Willing to go?</a></li>
<li><a href="#simple-security-measures">Simple Security Measures</a>
<ol>
<li><a href="#browser-add-ons">Browser Add-ons</a></li>
<li><a href="#firewalls">Firewalls</a></li>
<li><a href="#encryption-in-communication">Encryption in Communication</a></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li><a href="#moderate-difficulty-actions">Moderate Difficulty Actions</a>
<ol>
<li><a href="#gpg">GPG - Encrypt on your own!</a></li>
<li><a href="#vpn-and-network-routing">VPN Services and Network Routing</a></li>
</ol>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="what-do-you-want-to-hide">What do you Want to Hide?</h3>
<p>An <em><strong>asset</strong></em> is something you value and want to protect. In the context of digital security, an asset is usually some kind of information. for example, your emails, contact lists, instant messages, location (current and past), and all files you come into contact with are all possible assets. Your devices may also be assets.</p>
<ul>
<li>Make a list of your assets: data that you keep, where it&rsquo;s kept, who has access to it, and what stops others from accessing it.<br>
: Notable entities you should be wary of is large companies such as Google or Amazon. These two companies alone own an absurdly large portion of the services available on the internet.</li>
</ul>
<p>Also be wary of those physically near you, think about what you may have locally accessible via your phone or laptop, is it protected from people that can grab your device out of your ownership? What&rsquo;s your solution if your device is stolen?</p>
<h3 id="how-bad-are-the-consequences-if-i-fail">How bad are the Consequences if I Fail?</h3>
<p>There are many ways that an adversary could gain access to your data. for example, an adversary can read your private communications as they pass through the network, or they can delete or corrupt your data.<br>
the motives of adversaries differ widely, as do their tactics. A government trying to prevent the spread of a video showing police violence may be content to simply delete or reduce the availability of. In contrast, a political opponent may wish to gain access to secret content and publish that content without your knowing.<br>
Think about every law you have broken on the internet, or every law you have talked about breaking on the internet.. Or any photos of broken laws to that point. Living in the U.S.A, all your information is intercepted and stored on servers for potential review.<br>
Security planning involves understanding how bad the consequences could be if an adversary successfully gains access to one of your assets. To determine this, you should consider the capability of you adversary. For example, your mobile phone provider has access to all your phone records. A hacker on an open Wi-Fi network can access your unencrypted communications. Your government might have stronger capabilities.</p>
<ul>
<li>Write down what your adversary might want to do with your prvate data.<br>
:</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="how-likely-is-it-that-i-will-need-to-protect-it">How Likely is it That I will Need to Protect it?</h3>
<p><em><strong>Risk</strong></em> is the likelihood that a particular threat against a particular asset will actually occur. It goes hand-in-hand with capability. while your mobile phone provider has the capability to access all of your data, the risk of them posting your private data online to harm your reputation is low.<br>
It is important to distinguish between what might happen and the probability it may happen. For instance, there is a threat that your building might collapse, but the risk of this happening is far greater in San Francisco (where earthquakes are common) than in Stockholm (where they are not).<br>
Assessing risks is both a personal and subjective process. Many people find certain threats unacceptable no matter the likelihood they will occur because the mere presence of the threat at any likelihood is not worth the cost. In other cases, people disregard high risks because they don&rsquo;t view the threat as a problem.</p>
<ul>
<li>Write down which threats you are going to take seriously, and which may be too rare or too harmless (or too difficult to combat) to worry about.<br>
:</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="how-much-am-i-willing-to-go-through-to-try-to-prevent-potential-consequences">How Much Trouble am I Willing to go Through to try to Prevent Potential Consequences?</h3>
<p>There is no perfect solution for security. Not everyone has the same priorities, concerns, or access to resources. Your <em><strong>risk assessment</strong></em> will allow you to plan the optimal strategy for you, balancing convenience, cost, and privacy.<br>
For example, an attorney representing a client in a national security case may be willing to go to greater lengths to protect communications about that case, such as using encrypted email, than a mother who regularly emails her daughter funny cat videos.</p>
<ul>
<li>Write down what option you have available to you to help mitigate your unique threats. Note if you have any financial constraints, technical constraints, or social constraints.<br>
:</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="security-planning-as-a-regular-practice">Security Planning as a Regular Practice</h3>
<p>Keep in mind your security plan can change as your situation changes. Thus, revisiting your security plan rfrequently is good practice.</p>
<p> <br>
 <br>
 <br>
 <br>
 </p>
<h1 id="how-far-are-you-willing-to-go">How far are you Willing to go?</h1>
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<ol>
<li>No Protection <em><strong>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m the Pull-Out King!&quot;</strong></em></li>
<li>Simple Security Measures</li>
<li>Moderate Difficulty Actions</li>
<li>Hermit Level Security</li>
</ol>
<h3 id="no-protection-im-the-pull-out-king">No Protection <em><strong>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m the Pull-Out King!&quot;</strong></em></h3>
<p>The Internet is a large and dangerous place, think about it like the ocean, or an ice berg. You only see the very tippy-top of that bad-boy, and the rest is all mystery. You don&rsquo;t know what&rsquo;s going on in there, is any of it a threat to you? When you access a website, you are talking to severeal different computers and companies throughout the world, and without any protection, or action on your end. They will see anything and everything you do on the internet.</p>
<p>Would you trust a stranger with your porn history?</p>
<h3 id="simple-security-measures">Simple Security Measures</h3>
<p>Simple security is the base minimum. The miniminum, in this case, however, is miles better than nothing.</p>
<h4 id="browser-add-ons">Browser Add-ons</h4>
<p>Any modern web browser should allow add-ons, or extensions. A strong recommendation would be to install something like Ublock or Privacy Badger. These use blacklists to avoid nefarious IP Adresses <!-- raw HTML omitted -->(websites, or elements on websites, visible or not)<!-- raw HTML omitted --></p>
<h4 id="firewalls">Firewalls</h4>
<p>While no longer a super important step to security, it does matter very much if you plan to install or access any services that aren&rsquo;t 100% transparent with you. Examples would be sharing files between computers on a local network, or installing any app from anywhere other than your designated app store/center  .</p>
<p>Firewall security will vary for every OS.</p>
<p>On <strong>Windows</strong>, I would highly recommend <strong>TinyWall</strong>. It&rsquo;s a simple systray app that will block all incoming internet by default. This is important, this means that nothing will be allowed in unless you explicitly allow it yourself.</p>
<p>On <strong>OSX</strong>, the system firewall should be good enough for operation. Upsettingly however, the firewall is turned off by default. All you have to do is go into the <strong>Security and Privacy</strong> section of your settings and then unlock and turn on the firewall! Voila! Off to the races.</p>
<p>On <strong>Linux</strong>, It is considered generally safe to leave alone, as the ports are all configured to off by default. To be sure though, as any app once installed, can activate these ports, we&rsquo;re going to get <strong>UFW</strong>. You should be able to grab it from your distribution&rsquo;s package manager. When trying to install you may notice two similar packages; UFW takes less power to run than GUFW, the only difference being GUFW gives you a graphical interface to work with. Once installed, the best measure is to insert these commands into your Terminal:</p>
<pre><code>sudo ufw default deny  

sudo ufw allow from 192.168.0.0/24  

sudo ufw limit ssh  

sudo ufw enable  
</code></pre><p>Then all you have to do is check that it&rsquo;s still running!</p>
<pre><code>sudo ufw status  
</code></pre><h4 id="encryption-in-communication">Encryption in Communication </h4>
<p>When communicating on the internet, it is important to be aware of what channels you are going through, as well as who can see it. A lot of more modern e-mail clients and instant messagers will provide encryption of some sort. This however is never a true guarantee. For instance, Google claims to encrypt all of your emails and chats, but they still have the capability to open up and view those very texts, as well as deliver them to any respective government.</p>
<p>When speaking to your friends and family it is all good and well to use your email provier&rsquo;s encryption, but don&rsquo;t for any second believe that they won&rsquo;t give it up if it contains incriminating information or <em><strong>tag</strong></em> it for <em><strong>fingerprinting</strong></em>.</p>
<p><em><strong>fingerprinting</strong></em> is generally a term to define when a website or service tries to identify you through all the information it can gather from your web browser (or other windowed internet-application), being your Location, IP Address, Web Browser, Web Browser Version, Operating system, GPS Signal, any access granted to the microphone or webcam, on, and on&hellip;. (We give our web browsers access to our entire computers these days&hellip;)</p>
<p>In my case, I like to use that word to define anyone or anything on the internet trying to harvest data about you or your device without permission or warning.</p>
<p>Companies like Google or Amazon will gladly sell all of your information to ad agencies for the sake of making easy money. If you ever wonder <em>&ldquo;How do companies stay afloat with all these free services, just as good as they paid ones?&quot;</em> It&rsquo;s because they aren&rsquo;t free, you&rsquo;re the product, and the agencies are using these services as a way to buy you out!</p>
<p>So, what can you do?</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t worry about it too much! Don&rsquo;t want people stealing your conversations? Try finding an e-mail service that YOU pay for, and if you ever have to send sensitive information over the internet, encrypt it yourself!</p>
<h3 id="moderate-difficulty-actions">Moderate Difficulty Actions</h3>
<p>Moderate security could be considered the &ldquo;Goldilocks Zone&rdquo; of security, it&rsquo;s not absurdly hard, but it will be decent enough to keep yourself free of local government, ISPs, and peeping toms.</p>
<h4 id="gpg">GPG &ndash; Encrypt on your own!</h4>
<p>GPG, or Gnu Privacy Guard, is a F.O.S.S program that one can use to essentially password protect their communications, files, or traffic! <em><strong>How do we do it??</strong></em></p>
<p>On <strong>Windows</strong> you would use a software like <strong>Gpg4win</strong>. This is an app that refers to itself as not a app, but simply an installation package [for other packages]. This is a group of packages put together to help apply encryption to all your communications. On it&rsquo;s website it lists these options as:</p>
<ul>
<li>GnuPG</li>
<li>Kleopatra</li>
<li>GNU Privacy Assistant (GPA)</li>
<li>GnuPG for Outlook (GPgOL)</li>
<li>GPG Explorer eXtension (GpgEX)</li>
<li>Claws Mail</li>
</ul>
<p>These additional add-ons are actually pretty convenient! They allow you to create a more fluid experience with your desktop and GPG!<br>
<strong>Kleopatra</strong> as described by the website&rsquo;s supplied PDF as, <em>&ldquo;The central certificate administration of Gpg4win, which ensures uniform user navigation for all cryptographic operations.&quot;</em> Broken down, it&rsquo;s a key-handler, so it&rsquo;ll be kind of like a password manager, or a identity library.<br>
<strong>Gnu Privacy Assistant</strong> is also present, which seems to be the same thing as Kleopatra, simply by the naming scheme this one seems safer.<br>
<strong>GnuPG for Outlook</strong> and <strong>GPG Explorer eXtension</strong> are add-ons to the system. The first allowing you to sign and encrypt messages, and the latter for doing the same in your <strong>File Explorer</strong>.<br>
<strong>Claws Mail</strong> is a lightweight, GPG enable*-able* e-mail client comparable to **Thunderbird**. *<!-- raw HTML omitted -->Which you can also use with encryption<!-- raw HTML omitted -->*</p>
<p><strong>Setting up after installation</strong> is made pretty easy, all you have to do is (in the example we will be using..) open <strong>Kleopatra</strong> from the Start Menu. From the start, you will get an empty box. All you have to do is go to File→New Certificate. This will open a dialog box for you to pick between OpenPGP or X.509, I recommend you go with OpenPGP for the first time. You will be greeted with a Certificate Creation Wizard, first, it will ask for your name, email and a comment. If you are using this for your work (usually computer development, or banking or something like that, you can fill these honestly. Otherwise, there is no rule saying you have to fill all of these in or if they have to be your real name; which is good for anyone trying to evade laws, if in fact you ever are cracked (however extremely unlikely to ever even become a problem).<br>
The next window will show you your information, and then prompt you to create the key. Next you will have to enter a passphrase for said key. It is best to enter the password into the prompt, but never save it in any clear(unencrypted) text files on a device connected to any network (save it on a USB!).<br>
After all this, they key will begin generation. In order for this process to complete, you need to create entropy for the computer. This means clicking and typing all around, to encourage more data to be set into and out of the CPU to help it generate a key. This creation process, however, provides you with a nice little text box to type away gibberish in to your heart&rsquo;s content! Or at least until the generation is completed.<br>
Once the creation is completed, you will then be able to backup, send, or upload your key pair or certificate to other places for sharing and safe keeping. It is best to share your certificate, but never share your key pair with <em><strong>ANYONE</strong></em>.</p>
<p>On <strong>OS X</strong> there is a similar package called the <strong>GPG Suite</strong>, curated by, funnily enough, <strong>GPGTools</strong>. Installation will be close to exactly the same as on Windows, just prettier.</p>
<p>With <strong>Linux</strong> it&rsquo;s a little bit of a more different experience, but a lot simpler! You simply have to install the <!-- raw HTML omitted -->gnupg<!-- raw HTML omitted --> package, and hopefully it&rsquo;ll give you all the dependencies, if not, try installing <!-- raw HTML omitted -->pinentry<!-- raw HTML omitted -->. After that, you can begin creation! Type in <!-- raw HTML omitted -->$ gpg &ndash;full-gen-key<!-- raw HTML omitted -->, this will prompt you for your name, e-mail, and any comments. With any other questions, the default is plenty fine. Once generation begins, simply click and type around the desktop to help it make the keys! Once it&rsquo;s generated, it is saved to your home directory and accessible to you throughout your system!<br>
One thing to note with Linux, is that any application that supports GPG requires setting up, though there is plenty of documentation on the internet about how to do it with any service you may please.</p>
<h4 id="vpn-and-network-routing">VPN Services and Network Routing</h4>
<p><strong>VPN</strong> or <strong>Virtual Private Network</strong> refers to a secondary router, or server, that you can connect to before hitting your ISP or any other servers or websites on the internet. Getting a VPN service is much more recommended by myself, as it&rsquo;s easier maintenance for you, but also, each service provides instructions on how to set up their connection differently, and a lot of them provide failsafes that OS&rsquo;s don&rsquo;t seem to carry (like turning off the network if the VPN disconnects).</p>
<p>Another direction to take this in would be with Network Routing, the most common service known as <strong>Tor</strong>. This is an abbreviation for <strong>The Onion Router</strong>. What it does, is it creates a network of interconnected devices, all sharing data and traffic, making it hard for any action or click be traced back to any one person. To use this, it is highly recommend by everyone in the industry to stick with the TOR Browser, an application based off of Firefox made specifically to ensure anonymity (look back to fingerprinting).</p>
<h3 id="hermit-level-security">Hermit Level Security</h3>
<p>This section is for people that have something to hide. Are you a whistle blower? Are you looking to disrupt society a bit, and don&rsquo;t wanna leave a cookie trail? Go no further (or do if you dare) than this section here.</p>
<section class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes">
<hr>
<ol>
<li id="fn:1" role="doc-endnote">
<p><!-- raw HTML omitted -->pretty much copy/pasted or slightly changed the wording from their website, so yes, this is plagiarized material pretty much&hellip;<br>
*meant for personal use.<!-- raw HTML omitted --> <a href="#fnref:1" class="footnote-backref" role="doc-backlink">&#x21a9;&#xfe0e;</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</section>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
